How, how you been Charlie? It's been a while.
Yeah, it's been a bit, it's been a bit, um,
last time we talked was what, like at least four months ago.
Yeah. Something like that. Time goes by so fast.
I know. No man. Just been staying busy.
Just more of the same e-commerce.
Just kinda last time we talked, we talked about, you know,
getting a video editor on board
and kind of having that process and it's, it's a process.
So, yeah. I mean, we have one that's really good.
We cycled through like three or four of 'em. Mm-Hmm.
And this one is like, worth like three people. Mm-Hmm.
Um, we have a creative strategist
and then, um, a media buyer.
And so it's been good,
but we're just trying to really systematize
the, the playbook here.
And so it's, it's a lot. It's like refining it.
Um, you know, I've made courses,
but nothing compares to this.
You have to really refine your process and Sure.
It's getting better. I love it every day. I love it.
Because you're not just doing something once.
It's something that, you know, will be used and built upon.
So that's why I like it.
It's amazing, man. Um, so, we'll, we'll wait
for a few more people to join,
but, um, regardless of that, I'd love to just kind of,
you know, because other people are gonna watch this
recording as well 'cause they're in different time
Zones. Right. I think most people
are
just gonna watch the recording. Yeah.
But, um, yeah, we'll just keep it pretty casual.
Um, would love to kind of get your story.
'cause I don't even know your full story to be honest. Dude,
I don't even know my own story.
I, I swear. I think, yeah.
I mean, my story is all on YouTube. It is. Yeah,
It is. I'm looking at your channel
right now.
I mean, you haven't posted in three years,
but you, you got up to almost, you know, 41 K subscribers,
which is impressive.
Yeah. Why did you stop?
I just kind of took my own advice
and I was just not just doing what I was teaching
or I was doing what I was teaching.
So like, you know, I was teaching e-commerce
and I was like, oh, this is such a good opportunity.
You guys should do this as well. And I was doing it,
you know, side by side uhhuh.
But I had to make a choice
because making YouTube videos is,
you know, it's time consuming.
It's tough. And honestly, it was really,
I just knew it would be a more sellable thing
and more scalable to do e-commerce rather than me kind of
constantly thinking of a new topic to put on YouTube.
Interesting. The crappy part is
that I really miss YouTube and helping,
but I just wasn't ready for it because I didn't have a team.
Like, I was putting everything together myself.
I was hosh posh. So it was helpful,
but it was really draining.
But anyway, so I took my own advice
and just doubled down on e-commerce
and, you know, I've sold more product than
I ever have of courses.
Hmm. And then I, you know, doubled down again.
Um, you know, this year investing even more
and, you know, creating custom products.
And I feel like that's
probably the direction where I'd like to go.
And then once I have, like I said, a better, a better team
that is kind of in flow, then I would love to hop on
and just share and help.
But like, you know, for fun, not
because like, I need to sell something.
Yeah. You know, I just wanna do it just
'cause I actually really liked doing it.
Yeah. Um, but yeah.
Interesting. So when you were doing your YouTube channel,
have you, did you not have an
e-commerce business yet on that? Oh,
I did. Yeah. That's, that
was everything.
I mean, I had an e-commerce business that I was scaling
and like, I mean, some of, some of like,
the videos were ridiculous, but they were true.
I mean, during covid when everything was pumping Mm-Hmm.
You know, there was a week where I
netted like a hundred grand.
Yeah. And I was like, Hey, how I netted a hundred?
And they're like, if you're netting that much,
why are you doing YouTube?
And they were kind of true in a way, but in another way.
Like, I genuinely loved YouTube,
but all the strategies I was showing was real.
Um, but it was also exhausting.
Again, running all that while learning, while teaching
and trying to not get too involved in like,
'cause you're looking at your metrics.
Oh, did people like it? Oh,
did people not like, you know what I mean?
Yeah. So, oh, for sure. Yeah. So
You, you were, you were content,
you're actual content creator
and you're an e-commerce entrepreneur
and, you know, those are two different worlds
and require Yeah.
Uh, it's an, an insane amount of energy to
Get done. Yes. Uhhuh
and you and yeah. And you just kind of, yeah.
It's hard. It's, it's hard if you don't have a good, uh,
a process and people to help
and I didn't have either. Got it.
Got it. For, for the, uh, content creation side
or for the e-com side?
To be honest, probably a little bit of both.
Like with e-commerce, like I still had people to help,
but it's like nothing compared to what I have now.
Like, with your process,
like a system is almost worth more than people.
So, um, yeah. Kind of both.
I mean, definitely for content creation, I mean,
I was the product, you know? Yeah,
Absolutely.
Um, so do you have plans to go back to YouTube Eventually?
Yeah. Like eventually I would like to,
but I would probably start really light
and small, just like a couple things here and there.
'cause I, I wanna plan it out
and have a little bit of a structure of like,
what would be my goal and what would make me happy.
Mm-Hmm. Um, 'cause I do miss it.
I love like, helping
and that was probably the most fulfilling is
just, it helped a lot of people.
I mean, like I said, you know, I've sold courses.
I have, I don't know how many students,
but let's just say a thousand.
There's a lot in there that, I mean, it's changed their life
and it's like something that you can't do.
Like with e-commerce, you know, you kind of put a wall,
like no one knows who I am when I'm selling my products.
Right. But when I'm selling like, information
and trying to help with coaching,
it's really fulfilling and kind of cool.
So I kind of wanna integrate that back.
I love that. And I've been on both sides of it all. Yeah.
I think community is huge.
You know, seeing, seeing
that you're making an impact in someone's life
is like, probably the best.
It's like acts of service, you know, I,
I believe in e-commerce, it's a different type of challenge.
You are helping people at a distance, right? Yes.
And, um, and,
and there's a, it's a whole nother set of systems
and challenges that you're faced with.
But I think ultimately as like an entrepreneur, you're,
you're kind of filling in all those gaps, you know?
'cause like being a content creator,
you're kind of like a solopreneur.
Like you're not really, you don't need
big teams and stuff like that.
People, you're, it's just dependent on yourself.
But then you get into e-comm, it's like fulfillment.
You have logistics, you have so many different parts
of the business that you're operating at the same time.
Um, so can you walk us through and what's up Chan?
Good to see you, man. Um, can you walk us through your,
like, your path to, you said exiting your a, a brand, right?
Yes. I mean, that one. Yeah. Shoot.
Uh, I should probably clean up that story a little bit,
but if I'm to walk you through it, shoot, I mean,
it was all hush posh.
I mean, that was one of my first brands I started.
Um, honestly, it was, it was drop shipping.
Like, I had basically two products.
It was all drop shipping. It was doing really well.
I don't want to, I don't want to say the, I don't know
what I'm allowed to say as far as like,
I wish I could just say the brand and the niche,
but I signed, I signed an NDA once I, you know,
did all that for sure.
So started with drop shipping,
just sold the product literally
through Google Ads, exactly what I taught.
And I was like, well, that's going well.
Then I scaled in on Facebook ads and Google ads,
and then I was like, well, let me make this product custom.
Hmm. So the biggest shift was when I made it custom
and unique because after you get a lot
of responses from customers, like, let's just say, you know,
Hey, I, I like the product, but I wish it had this feature.
Or for example, like, if you're getting a lot of returns,
because if you have a battery product
and it's dying, you could literally increase your margin
because, you know, you're adding a, an upgraded battery for,
you know, 20 cents a piece.
And so there's a lot of easy wins that you can do.
So I customize the product. I love design.
So we designed it even better, and it just looked
and felt better.
And in your ad, that's really important.
You kind of need something to stand out. Yep.
Then once we did that, uh, it went really well.
Um, up until, honestly,
I don't know, up until it just kind of started dying off.
I mean, there was a point where like, so long story short,
I, I got, I ran through a glass wall,
and so I was like, long story short, I, I couldn't type,
like, I, I didn't even have a hand. Well, you
Actually ran through a glass wall.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So like, like
I thought that was like a metaphor.
No, no, no.
Like, yeah, i, i, it literally, like,
I, I ran through a glass wall.
I went to the hospital, so I couldn't actually type
and work on the business for like, four months.
Wow. And so, like, I would still work on it,
but I was, it, it was kind of screwed up.
So, long story short, um, it kind
of started dying off, like, as you would imagine.
And I was like, dude, I should really sell this thing.
Mm-Hmm. And so this was two and a half years into it,
and since it was a custom product, since we patented it,
design patented it and everything, it still had value.
And it was still making about, you know,
a million bucks a year in profit.
Nice. And so it was still valuable, but it was dying off.
And so because of that, um, you know, I only sold it
for 2.3, which isn't great, but it's not terrible.
So my biggest lesson was, you know, get better timing.
So I need to, I, if I would've launched more products
and I would've shown a trend, it could've sold for way more.
'cause I had a lot of history.
So now
what I wanna do is just do all custom products launch at
least one to two new products a year for that brand
or for any brand, and then just keep logging the fire.
So,
Wow. That's impressive.
It's, it, it,
I think that's the pinnacle, right?
You start a brand and you, you exit and you sell.
It's, it's not really what talked about that much,
because I think it, it, it's a hard thing
to reach for a lot of brands.
Hmm. Um, they're kind of stuck in the, like, they're either
I need to get this to sell, or I can't scale it further.
And, you know, they don't even reach that point
where they're like, okay, let's talk about
how can we sell this thing.
But it sounded like you were in a position
where you're like, okay, I don't have much choice
because I'm disabled. Like
Physically I can't.
Yeah. I mean, the way, I mean, yeah, it was crazy.
I was just playing basketball
and I live at a place that's like surrounded by glass.
Mm-Hmm. And around the whole basketball court is
like glass walls.
So I, I literally, I barely tapped a 10 foot glass wall
with my hand, and it came shattering
and it was, it could open my head, my neck,
and it sliced my tendon on my hand.
That's why. And I was in like a thick cast,
and so it was extremely, and it was my right hand.
It's extremely annoying. But yeah, I mean,
what saved me was just having like a unique product
and angle and being able to sell the story to the buyer.
Mm-Hmm. Because when you're selling your brand,
you're selling a story of why this is a good deal for them.
Mm-Hmm. So for them to acquire and say, oh yeah,
because of X, Y, and Z, it's gonna still scale.
Correct. Um, so, you know, that's, that's kind
of like the newest strategy because not a lot of people are,
first of all, making their own custom products
or even finding something that's profitable.
Um, and it's really valuable to people
that truthfully have a lot, a lot of money,
but are also lazy.
Like, they don't wanna really do that part.
Yeah. So have you followed up with the brand
and are they doing better than how you left it?
No. Oh yeah.
I mean, look, when people take over companies most
of the time, yeah.
I mean, it, it's, it's not, I don't know
how much I'm allowed to say, but Yeah. No.
Got it. I mean, I've heard,
I've heard a lot of horror stories.
I think acquisitions are, are, they could be strategic
or just financial base
and depending on who you hand it over to.
Yeah. Like the, the organization just seems to fall apart
because leadership changes and everything too.
Yeah. It's, it's tough to like transfer over like
the secret sauce or the playbook.
Like, people have their own stubborn ways.
They're like, no, I'm gonna run it like this. Mm-Hmm.
And in a way, you don't wanna fight the buyer
because the buyer is buying it
because they think they have a genius idea.
Correct. And so, like, I don't know, like, yeah.
I wish I, I wish the brand could thrive.
'cause you know, I pretty much grew up
with the brand, at least part of me did.
Right. Yeah. So, um, it's an interesting dynamic
and I'm excited to get more experience in that side,
but I think there's a lot of opportunity in that.
It's not something AI can wipe out, you know? Yeah.
AI's not gonna wipe out physical products.
So that's why I feel like it's a, a longevity play too.
I love that. And so from what you've built, um, like,
it sounds like you're on that journey again,
but how are you doing things differently this time?
Because it sounds like you wanna do it again, right?
Yeah. So differently. That's a good question.
Honestly, it feels like everything's different.
Um, what's different is every product,
first of all, every product that like does really well,
you're gonna have auxiliary products.
So you, like I said
before, you wanna launch at least one to two products
to keep it, keep it going.
And so you wanna have a product line.
And then once you have that, like, I haven't done this yet,
but then have consumable products so
that way you have a backend of people coming back.
Mm-Hmm. So your game is really just go
with your hero product, see how long it'll last.
Usually it should last about two years,
and then probably start dying off.
There's anomalies, there's, you know, plenty of brands
that are still going, but that's, that's one.
And then again, launch two products
or so, continue with that.
And then, I don't know, maybe
after three years look for a buyer.
Yeah. Because you kind of wanna look early.
Um, I mean, I wish I could say like, yeah,
after five years I'm gonna sell a huge,
but I just, I don't see that.
I feel like there's a better story where you're on the up.
It looks like you're growing a hundred percent,
your net margins are really good.
Repeat do it to the next.
I, I mean, yeah. I think that would, that's,
that's a good little strategy.
My, my question is like, what if, what, what has been your
challenges now going into it?
'cause I know we've talked a lot about
building teams and systems.
Has that been like, what have you learned
by doing that yourself this time?
I don't know. I think the biggest challenge is,
is like getting people on your team that, I don't know,
just have that like, execution factor.
Um, you don't want someone who's, I don't know,
you want someone that's along for the ride
and isn't looking for, like, I want a big company who's,
you know, nine to five
and they're looking for more structure rather
than, Hey, this is really fun.
I wanna be along for the journey.
So that's just something new for me.
Um, we've been doing better at that
because now I have a lot of help
and it's, it is so motivating to have people
that you genuinely like to talk to every day.
Mm-Hmm. Um, so I would say that's the toughest part is
because like, my time is now, like, I'm more
of like a manager, right?
I'm managing them and constantly giving them direction
and help and then making new videos and,
and then making SOPs.
And that, that takes a lot of time.
Um, I would say that's probably the hardest.
But once I get out of that stage
and I, you know, build the foundation for the house,
you know, putting in all the furniture is easy,
but that foundation takes a really long time.
So,
Yeah. So
when you started your first company,
did you not have like, SOPs
and a lot of team members? No. Really?
No. Interesting.
So I always thought that you had to have all of
that in order to sell.
Oh, oh, no, no, no.
That and the, the company
that I sold wasn't even my first company.
My first company was, uh, BFF Ware.
It was like, you know, put your face on socks,
put your face on boxers, uhhuh, it was a customizable gift.
No, that was my first one.
And you know, we had like 15
to 20 designers on the team and Mm-Hmm.
It was, uh, custom products. And that was really hard.
And, and for the other one that I sold, no,
there was no SOPs.
Like it was, you know, everyone knew their internal process.
We had SOPs for how to respond
to different customers for customer service.
Mm-Hmm. But yeah, I mean, no, I mean,
it was kind of a simple business too.
Like, there wasn't many SKUs.
I mean, there was literally three SKUs. So.
Interesting. Wow. Yeah. Okay.
So I think that's helpful for a lot of people
who have, who are running brands.
Um, so let's talk about possibly like
creatives creative strategy, um,
and how you've been working with your team members on
that team, and what's the good and the bad and the ugly
Dude creatives. That's
why I'm here. Right? I'm learning from you.
Um, creatives, we're, we're testing, we're kind
of doing a blend of VSLs
and then creatives that has worked for me in the past.
So like, I like two minute long videos.
But I mean, I, I've never, what I would love
to know from people in the group is if they've ran 30 minute
VSLs and it's made a night and day difference.
Because for me, we run two minute videos and it crushes.
And those like two minute VSL videos,
it'll last like four or five months.
Mm-Hmm. And it's really good. Yeah.
And we just cycle in new hooks.
Um, yeah, I mean the, the creative process,
honestly, we, we have a full Monday board
and it, it's a little bit lengthy.
So, you know, we're still kind of narrowing down
how I can make it to where our video editor
and creative strategist can kind of do all of
that rather than me adding in like my marketing side.
'cause it's, uh, it can get very time consuming.
But right now, two minute videos, refresh, hooks,
repeat. It's kind of simple.
Yeah, for sure.
So, uh, with the VSLs, I mean the, the 30 minute thing I,
I couldn't tell you 'cause I haven't done it myself.
Um, I imagine, are you, do,
do you have like a long form VSL on the lander?
No. Is that what you're talking about?
Or running it as a top of funnel? Okay.
No, yeah. We, we run to like presale pages.
So presale page to then bundle page, I mean, exactly.
Kind of what I taught even on YouTube. Mm-Hmm.
Um, still running that, but just making everything clean.
So, you know, everything that
I run is always custom content.
So the mo the models, the pro, um,
any animations that's custom.
So everything is always custom.
I found that to be really helpful to kind of set you apart.
Um, but yeah, I mean it's, yeah. Creatives in that side.
Again, I'm not a professional in that at all.
Um, so I guess with the, with your team right now,
you say you have a strategist and an editor, right?
Yeah. Um, and you're probably coming in, chiming in, um,
where people are missing a lot. Yeah.
Yeah. It ain't, it's not streamlined. Yeah.
We're, we're, we're working on it. I love it. Yeah.
Um, yeah, no, it is, it is.
I think, um, you know,
no one can ever replace your experience.
Right. And I think people have to grow on their own.
Like when you have team members, like for me, for instance,
um, my team members, you know, it took 'em like a year
to like really kind of level out, up to a certain point.
And then there's a, there's also like people
who just have it in instinctively, you know,
who have that edge.
Um, I would say sparse is one of those guys.
Um, you just, like, when you, when you, oh, there we go.
Love it when you live it
and breathe it, like it shows in your work.
Right. Um,
and so, yeah, I think So are you shooting
everything in-house right now?
Are you building? Yes. Okay. So how is that going for you?
So by in-house, do you mean like literally like scheduling
locations and shooting it with like our own
videographer? Is that what you mean?
Yes, and or like UGC creators?
Yeah. So both. Okay, cool.
So I feel like we kind of, we do a blend of both.
So we'll have like our own shot lists and everything,
but yeah, we, we like to schedule locations.
So like, for example, I mean, it sounds funny,
but I was in Newport for a good amount of time
and it was a nice place.
And I was like, dude, let's just schedule some models here.
I mean, might as well. Mm-Hmm.
And we got a lot of good content
because when you're getting stuff from like UGC creators,
I haven't mastered, like, they're good,
but I don't know, I still need like, our own custom content
where we're there kind of guiding the process.
And I don't know, maybe I'm not doing a good enough job
for the shot list, but like, it's hard
to find really good UGC creators.
So we're trying to create a database.
I know I kind of talked to you about
that a little bit, but, Mm-Hmm.
It's, it is a slow build process. Yeah.
Um, but we, we, yeah, we, we blend them both.
Yeah, I agree. And I've spoken to a few people about it.
And Kale, if you don't mind chiming in,
I don't know if you work with UGC creators, but, um,
but yeah, you know, it, it's a tossup.
It's, it's kind of a crapshoot. Everybody is at different
Skill levels, Right?
Yeah. Um, some people know how to shoot, some people don't.
Some people say they do,
and then you have life that gets in the way.
So like, delivery could be up and down. Um, interesting.
But in terms of like scalability, like yes,
you have like infinite reach of creators.
Um, I, I do prefer a blend,
especially if like, we're strapped on time.
Um, so with with with UGC creators, I,
I usually brief them like on on one-on-one call,
or Ah, yeah.
So I provide them either with a loom going over everything,
or I'll speak to them directly.
'cause like I said, you're, you're dealing with people now.
It's like having an additional set of team members
that you have to align your vision with.
Because I've done it too, where I'm just like,
I hand it over to them and then I get back.
I'm like, what just happened? Like, yeah.
I'm like, all right, you, you just shoot the videos.
Don't edit it all right. Yeah.
Just like, just leave, leave it, leave us to that.
But, um, but yeah, like I said, um, alignment is everything.
Um, there.
I, I see, I foresee,
and a lot of people are talking about, this is like finding
just your, your little crew of, of UGC creators
that you are, you can depend on Yes.
Yeah. That are reliable. And then
that becomes like they understand what you're looking for.
Um, and then it's more consistent pay for them as well. Um,
I agree. And
I like that. And I like having like a, a system,
let me mute this, hang on.
And like, one system that we do, we use a jot form. Mm-Hmm.
One sec. And that kind
of takes the creator through a process.
So we'll put a loom on top of the, like for jot form,
and then questions be like, you know,
will you have someone help you an extra $25 if you can
to help you film, um, nice lighting.
So that's actually really helped.
Um, and so I, I love the loom.
We just try, I just try to systematize it
so we don't have to make a new one every time.
Um, yeah. But yeah,
building a database is extremely valuable.
And I think, yeah, you should,
you should eventually consider either outsourcing your
database to people here for a fee.
I mean, it's, it's hard.
Yeah, definitely.
We've been in talks about it,
we're just working out the details.
But before, um, Khale leaves, he has a question for you.
He has a marketing agency transferring into a brand house.
I was wondering if, about your current process
of her product research, do you seek
to create something entirely unique off the bat?
No. So you wanna innovate off of what's working.
So start slow. So whatever you test, like you don't want
to go and create something completely unique, you know, um,
go test, you know, test something
that is a normal drop shipping product,
see if there's any viability.
And even before that, I should say,
what I do is I do what's called a purchase demand test.
So I'll actually gather like seven to 10 stores,
and I will place an order on each of those stores.
Uhhuh, I'll place an order, and then I'll cancel. Okay.
So you have an email, you, you cancel,
and then you get their order number.
Then you wait seven days, use a different email,
place an order cancel again.
Then you subtract the orders, divide by seven.
And then you know which one is doing really well
for like orders per day.
And then you kind of narrow in
and say, okay, where is my opportunity?
Where can I actually innovate?
You know, where would be my skillset?
So, you know, once you kind
of did your purchase demand test, you can,
you have a good idea of where to go from there.
And then you can see, all right, what would be my margin
for a product if I was to sell it?
Then you test it and see, you know, uh,
if you're getting consistent sales and then innovate
and kind of do the custom product
while you're kind of drop shipping.
Wow. For me, I mean, I don't even, I,
I follow the first part of my advice,
which is the purchase demand test.
And then I kind of go ballsy
and I say, f**k it, I'm gonna make a custom product.
So, but I'm okay with that, you know, kind
of risking it at this point.
Um, but for most, I feel like the first stage is safer.
That's wild. Uh, is
that your own proprietary way of doing things?
I mean, that's one of 'em. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's, that's one of them.
And I think that'll be helpful for people. Um, but ma yeah.
Making custom products and going through that whole process.
Yeah. It's, I mean, you'd be surprised at
how many different things work.
Um, I mean, there's, you can go as complicated
as you want or as simple as you want.
I mean, there's, like, for example, there's a guy
that I know very, it,
it's annoying how well this is working.
And he has a, a air pump. It's a portable air pump. Mm-Hmm.
And selling one product,
and it's doing like 700 grand a month.
And then they're putting it on Amazon.
It's 300 grand a month, one product, a simple product.
But then of course there's other products like, you know,
in the pain industry
and wherever else where it's more complicated.
So I feel like, yeah, eventually just find a product
that kind of matches your personality
and style of what you'd be interested in selling as well.
That'd probably be my final filter.
Amazing. So with your current situation,
I know you're running into like compliance issues.
Did you Yeah.
Come back. So, yeah.
See now that's a, that's a black hole, but yeah.
So one of the products that we have is in weight loss.
I, I don't even know if I should say we have it.
'cause we, we launched it, it crushed, it did really well.
Then after anyone in weight loss will understand this
completely, after July, all
of a sudden all these ad rejections started happening
and getting worse and worse.
Now we're at a point where I can't even launch an ad
that I see someone else already running.
So I can't that that business is completely on hold now
as far as figuring out that issue.
Yes. Um, the thing is, is
that it's not the way I'd like to figure it out.
It's a little bit, I don't like to go black hat. So Yes.
I mean, if I really wanted to. Yeah. But it's, it's crazy.
You, you will not be able
to run weight loss products on Facebook.
I mean, it's insane. It, and it just changed. Um, yeah.
Yeah. It's, it's pretty,
it's pretty aggressive out there for sure.
In that, uh, so is that product tied to your overall brand
or is that like a separate brand?
No, it's a separate brand. Okay.
This thing took, this thing took a year and a half.
We have about 150 grand in inventory.
'cause I mean, it was working and we were selling.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. And, and now it's just sitting there
and it's just collecting dust
because we, we can't, I mean, I've tried, I've tried
to even do, TikTok doesn't like it.
Pinterest doesn't like it.
Pinterest banned, um, weight loss,
TikTok banned weight loss.
Um, we tried to put it on YouTube.
YouTube keeps giving us these errors.
We, we can't even get it on YouTube.
Um, and I was like, well, I see five companies
that are good companies that are still on, uh, weight loss.
So we're doing a lot of investigation
on like, how they're doing.
And now I'm just now as
of the last like 48 hours getting closer
to figuring out this rabbit hole.
And I'll decide if I wanna move forward with it.
But weight loss is extremely tough.
Beauty is tough, but not impossible.
But weight loss, I would say is almost impossible
unless you have like a really high up like
rep in your ad account for weight loss.
But to have that, you had
to have started like three-ish years ago to build up a rep.
Like we have a good rep in, you know, different brand.
But yeah, I mean, it's,
it's kind of, yeah, it's crazy.
Yeah. I mean,
I still see really shady stuff being
sold on the weight loss side. I just, I really
Send it my way. I wanna,
I wanna see what the heck they're doing.
Um, reverse engineer,
Well, I don't know. I mean,
it, it is sketchy
'cause it's like I'm pretty, I mean,
it's all black hat kind of stuff. Yeah.
It's, you know, it's, it's a means to an end.
It's just not worth it. Like, you know, we don't, I mean,
our feedback score was a 4.4.
I mean, people loved it. They were very happy.
I mean, it's a weight loss slash fit fitness, so, you know,
we're not selling creams and potions that don't work.
Um, but yeah, I mean, I don't know.
It's, uh, I don't have an answer for it yet.
I'm still just, just still in the middle of it.
Yeah. Is it, is it claims or just overall the, the niche?
No, it's, no, it's literally like, you could,
you can run a blank video.
So I'll, I'll submit the blank video
to the landing page and everything.
And that's fine. As soon as you put any overlaying text,
and you might be like, well, well, Charlie, don't,
don't use, you know, this text, I'm telling you,
it's the most dumbed down text.
Like, for example, you know, meet the brand name
that gets disapproved.
And I'm, it's, it's getting like, it's very odd.
Um, again, I don't have a good answer.
So, you know, I've, I've gone to the extent
of literally I have a Google sheet,
like looking scientifically, okay, we took out this text,
this text, and trying to figure it out methodically.
It's, uh, yeah, I have like almost a full course in the SOPs
on just that, on how to figure things out.
Like we went really deep.
Um, I mean, now
what I think people are doing is they're just getting
insiders to approve their ad and then they just run it.
Right. Damn.
Well the other brand is picking up the slack there then.
That's what it sounds like that
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean that's, that's what it is right now.
I mean, I can't, yeah, exactly. It's something I could do.
Um, but mainly, you know, the next, the next steps
for me is just, I don't know,
I'm just investing a lot into like,
brands that I wanna launch.
So I'm, I'm creating, I don't know how many, at least four
to five different custom products that I are supposed
to be like my front end hero products.
Mm-Hmm. You know, for different industries that, you know,
I'm just risking, I think I've put in like 700 already
and just saying, let's see what happens.
Yeah. Um, because I believe that if you just can get
that momentum, kind of like what I said earlier,
get the momentum, sell the story,
and then you can sell the brand.
I just wanna see what will happen. I'm just curious.
I don't know. I love that.
So you're gonna get to a point where you're gonna need
to hire more people, right. 'cause
Hopefully, yeah.
Unless it all crumbles, then yeah. I'm good.
Yeah. Um, so I, I would say right now
for the creative side are like, are there any, I mean,
you talked about bottlenecks,
but, um, like how much more room
for scale do you think there is for your,
the product you're running right now?
Uh, room for scale. What do you mean?
Like, by like revenue, like you mean
how much can you rephrase it? What do you mean?
So were you guys like, like do you see yourselves
like doubling, tripling, like seeing the Oh, no,
No, no. Look,
with one product,
you're not gonna just double revenue
without cutting your margin.
Mm-Hmm. And so I'm not gonna cut my margin.
There's no point. Um, you know, like usually, like I said,
so I'll, I'll usually net a couple mill a
year and that's good.
But I feel like if you do this strategy
where you have multiple products, you could, you know,
kind of three x that.
And so look
after a while, look, I think if I just kept
this one business, how it is,
it'll probably finish off the year 20% less.
Hmm. And plus, with the way everything is going
with the market, it's just not,
there's nothing that's gonna give it a boost.
In order to give it a boost, you have to launch new stuff.
Got it. Um, most people say like,
their business grows year over year,
but really they're just cutting into their margin.
Mm-Hmm. You know, I, I talk to a lot of people
that are doing, you know, way bigger numbers
and the only way they make money
is if they sell their business.
And these are like really big legit businesses.
And so they're, they're strapped for cash all the time.
And I just personally don't like that.
Um, I feel like it's a little bit more fun
to have like a lean team
and just try your strategies rather than always trying
to like, run from the wave of dead.
So, so no, I mean,
your product is inevitably gonna be gonna die.
Creatives is kind of your lily pad to keep it going.
So creatives are extremely important,
but you have to put fuel in the fire
and plant a seed for your next
vision of where you're gonna go.
And if you don't have that vision,
then now is the time to sell.
Because like, hoping that it just gets better.
Like, I just don't see it.
Um, so that's just where, yeah,
that's just my opinion. I love
That. Yeah. No,
that's really smart.
I mean, you're thinking ahead. Um, so
with these new products, are they closely related?
Are they tapping into a completely different
Audience? They're so different.
Yeah. Under one brand? No, no.
This, oh no, completely. No, I'm okay. Gotcha. Yeah.
So no, to be transparent, so I only have one brand
that is active, one brand that weight loss, right?
Weight loss is inactive.
And then, you know,
I have another brand, but I don't even count that.
And then I'm launching, uh, i, I believe three brands
with the front end hero products.
So they'll do really well in the beginning. Mm-Hmm.
But to be transparent, like that's, that's the goal, right?
To launch those, um, into different verticals.
'cause that's how you're gonna get the
most, you know, squeeze.
But when you launch auxiliary products inside your
whatever main brand mm-hmm.
It's good. But, um, that's just gonna keep you afloat
and growing little by little.
I see. Um, but your,
your biggest squeeze is obviously gonna be a completely
different, uh, vertical.
Yeah. Um, I don't want to be like too scattered though.
So that's why we're kind of starting small
and building, right.
We have our own little playbook,
but at the end of the day,
you know, we will see what happens. I don't know,
I love It. Like, I
hope it works,
but so far that's kind of been what I've been doing
for the last, you know,
five years without really knowing it.
You know, you're just kind of scaling
new products and new brands.
And then, um, if I was smart enough,
I would've sold the other two that I
had, you know, way back when.
So when you do reach your goals,
which I'm confident you will, what is, what is that outcome?
What is it that you're, are you,
are you just literally allowing universe to kind
of like, put it together for you?
Or like, is there a certain number
or goal goalposts that you want to hit?
No, I feel like, I feel like goals are really good
to have, but like, I just try to put as much
as I can in each day
and see where the steps kind of guide me.
Like, I know generally where I want to go, right?
I wanna, you know, sell at least my next sale.
I want it to be between five to 10. Okay.
And then maybe the next sale
after that will be in the same range, if not more.
But I could only do as much as I could do.
So my next step is to just treat each day doing as much
as I can, systematizing everything,
and creating a really good base for something
that I feel like, you know, whichever direction I go,
this base I'm creating today will
always be here no matter what.
So this is the right decision, right.
I'm not going completely like, oh, well,
you know, tomorrow I'm gonna try crypto.
So I'm just, yeah. You know, I'm just staying consistent.
And then, yeah, I mean, as far as the goals, I just,
I'll just try my best each day
and then it'll get more clear.
Aw, gosh, that was, that felt very authentic and genuine.
Here we go. Yeah,
No, I mean, I think I personally felt,
and it's very touching to hear that from, from you,
especially after all that you've accomplished over,
you know, your, your career.
I think, um, you know, at the end of the day,
it's just putting in putting in the work every day
and just, you know, not getting too far ahead
or get stuck in the past.
Right. Yeah. I think I, I've suffered from both of those.
It's like, oh, I want this and that. When will I get that?
Or, oh s**t, this happened. This is holding me back. Yes.
It sounds like for you, you're just, look,
I'm gonna give it my all and
I'm gonna just gonna trust the process
And being honest with yourself.
Like, everyone knows if they had a good day at the gym,
like, did you actually go all out at the gym
or did you half-ass it.
So just being consistent, I feel like is the most important.
Like just people aren't consistent.
I feel like in this industry, it's a lot easier than
what people make it out to be.
You know? It's just, if you're just consistent, smart
and healthy, that's already gonna put
you ahead of a lot of people. Um,
I love that. That's
it. So, so talking about consistency
and that's something for sure I've been working on this
year, um, as like a lesson from last
year of being inconsistent.
Oh, there we go. What is kind of like,
I know everyone's different in different parts
of their life, um, but like, what is beyond business?
Like, what do you do for your own personal health,
personal growth to keep you in the right mindset?
Well, I work out a lot. So that's one.
Uh, I take a lot of supplements, so I'm just, I, I just try
to optimize my health.
So I, you know, I ate very clean.
I typically stick to,
I guess a keto diet, if that's what you'd say.
It's really just whole foods. Mm-Hmm.
I try not to go too deep into all that stuff.
I, I try to eat as clean as I can.
Everything organic, nothing processed.
Um, and that makes me feel better
and have less, I mean more energy.
I mean, really, I feel like energy
is almost worth more than time.
'cause if you're not energized, you're
not gonna do anything with your time anyway.
Mm-Hmm. So, so energy is really important for me.
I have like, I take like 60 different supplements.
Most of them is like B vitamins and there's NMN resveratrol.
There's, I kind of went really deep on that side.
But as far as consistency, I feel like the gym
and then just making sure that
you're happy with what you're building.
And if you feel like you're not happy,
you're not gonna be consistent with it anyway.
You're just, you really gotta kind of go deep down
and be like, like, I am I happy with this direction.
And if not, sometimes it's just a small tweak.
Doesn't mean you have to hop industries.
Um, you know, at one point I wasn't happy
with e-commerce and now I love it.
And the reason why I wasn't happy before is
'cause I was like, dude, I don't wanna sell s**t products.
Mm-Hmm. They're like, this seems like a means to an end.
So all I did was shift it
and I'm like, wait, I could actually make my own products.
I could, um, get to this point.
And I started that years ago.
And now I love it because I get to create it
and kind of create all the pieces on the chessboard
that I feel like, you know, I would really like
as a cool strategy.
Um, so you have to, you actually have to love
what you're doing, what you're building.
You can't avoid it no matter how much caffeine you take.
Mm-Hmm. So that kind of just naturally flows
with how I'm consistent.
And then, um, just being aware, you know,
if you're not feeling good, you know, after a week
or two weeks or you just have been kind of sluggish,
you need to kind of diagnose yourself
and see why, you know, are you seeing, like, are you happy
with the people you're around?
I mean, it's a deep topic.
I mean, I could talk on forever,
but it's really, it just comes down to clarity.
I mean, the more clarity you have,
the more happiness you'll have
and the more money you'll make.
Well, I think that's a really important topic.
'cause you know, we talk business all the time
and we talk strategy and all that stuff.
But you said something amazing there.
It's like, uh, your energy is more valuable than time.
'cause if you don't have energy, like you,
you can't utilize your time.
Yeah. Yeah. And,
and I know a lot of people here,
especially in the community, struggle
with staying consistent
or even having passion in what they're doing.
Um, including myself.
Uh, you know, I, it's funny how you brought up like, I used
to not like e-commerce because of this reason.
And then you switched your perspective of it
and started taking action,
and then you fell in love with it again.
There we go. And dude, I was the same way.
I was just getting burnt out.
I was like, why am I doing this? I want to be out of this.
And then I switched my perspectives like, wow,
like I can help a lot of people.
Yeah. Moment. I was like, I that flip switched
and I was like, this is what I'm supposed to be doing.
Um, but yeah, I think, you know, Chan has a question,
what do you mean by staying consistent?
I think, did he answer that or did
you want to elaborate on that?
Um, I know Chan has worked with other clients
and stuff that he isn't necessarily like super stoked about.
Um, but you, you mentioned like falling in love with,
with what you're doing.
And how would you go about like, defining that for somebody,
you know, like tapping into Yeah,
That's a, it's a, dude, it's one of the hardest things.
I mean, everyone struggles with it for a reason, right?
Because it's not easy. So, uh, you, I don't know.
I feel like your first step is to first become healthy.
And I, I, it sounds silly,
but if you cannot think clearly,
you're not gonna figure out a deep problem like this.
So first you gotta think, okay,
cutting out all the bad food, eating clean,
taking good vitamins, you know, all, all your B vitamins
and going clean, you know, for at least a couple weeks.
Okay. Then you get to see
how your body feels and how you feel.
But as far as, I don't know, man, it's tough.
Like, I think deep down, everyone already knows the answer.
They're just waiting for someone to tell them.
And I, it's like, it's, it's s****y
because the longer you wait, the harder it is
to break those chains.
And then the longer it, it just like,
it gets worse and worse.
And you come up with excuses on like,
well, it's not that bad.
Or, oh, I, well, I shouldn't, or I can't.
And it gets worse and worse.
And then once you finally rip that bandaid,
it'll feel great, but obviously really bad in the beginning.
And this can go for relationships.
This can go for your business.
And it, it, the problem is that it's not easy.
That's why a lot of people are silently miserable.
Um, so you have to really address where you want to go.
And I'm telling you, once you do, you will feel
so energized, so excited.
And then you'll be like, I get it.
It's hard to, it's like, it's hard to understand
how it feels until you feel it.
Right. And it's hard to understand that a business can work
until you start seeing it work.
Mm-Hmm. So you, you kind of just have
to like, trust that process.
But it's not easy. So I don't have a great answer,
but that's the idea, I guess.
Man, I, I resonate so much with that
and I know it will for a lot of people here.
Um, you know, I think that first step, like you said,
is like, well, you gotta be super honest with herself.
Right? I think, um, I have a, I have an actress who I work
with and she's gonna write a book and,
and she's gonna title it, go F**k yourself.
And then, but she's gonna cross out f**k and,
and write face, go face yourself.
Oh, nice. So it's about facing yourself
and being just relentlessly honest about every aspect
of your life, whether that's financial, personal, physical,
emotional, spiritual relationship, all
of those like cornerstones that we, you know,
we'll look in this direction, but we won't look at that,
you know, we'll neglect this.
And, and, and,
and like you said, like being healthy is the start.
It's like making a change in your life will, you know,
create this chain reaction.
Yeah. Or like a positive change,
whether it's quitting something, you know, it's like you,
you, you're putting this effort to like change your behavior
for the better, which will then create
another positive behavior.
Another positive behavior. Exactly.
Right. Yep. And, um,
and another thing you said about, um, detail,
we know Yeah.
And that, that really, like, that really hit me
because f**k, I've made a s**t ton of excuses about
who I want to be and what I want to do.
And it really, what I've,
after doing like deep meditation work
and like trauma healing
and that kind of stuff, man, it came down to, uh,
you know, imposter syndrome.
You know, not getting approval from my parents when I was
younger about just the things that I've been gifted with.
It's been kind of like shut down. Mm-Hmm.
Like my light has has been dimmed down
by them and I'm not blaming them.
Um, yeah, yeah, yeah. Interesting.
It just comes down to, okay, now I have to face the truth
that that is the reality.
Okay. Am I gonna play the victim, right.
Am I gonna allow their story, project it towards me
and let me live a very minimal life
because of what their values are
or am I'm gonna forgive them
and be like, okay, I see that you're doing that.
That's totally fine.
That's the way you wanna live your life.
I'm gonna take control of my life
and I'm going to do this regardless of how you think of me.
Yeah. And once I made that kind of realization is when,
oh f**k, they're not in control of like who I wanna be
and what I wanna become in this world.
Um, so sometimes it is,
it could be your past that's haunting you.
And um, and
that takes sometimes a whole a cold, honest look.
And like the people you love, like the closest people
to you are probably the ones that
are holding you back. Sometimes.
Sometimes that's true. Yeah. Yeah.
And I mean, uh, and at all times it's us holding us back
'cause we're the ones that making decision. So
Ultimately, yeah, we're in control.
Yeah. We gotta figure it out.
But I'm only, I'm only saying this
because like, it's not like I've avoided this.
I've gone through this, it s**t sucks. It's awful.
Um, and yeah, I mean, it, it is the thing
that I think has really helped me is the health part.
And I know people will skip over that,
but like, as you start to become healthier,
you will just feel more like you Mm-Hmm.
And you have to like really be able to analyze your emotions
quite critically in order for you
to make a, a serious decision.
And it is scary, you know, to make a decision.
So, but it'll feel better. I mean, start small.
But, um, the next step that I usually say is just like,
you have to write down things.
Most people are gonna forget about
half the stuff we even said.
Um, unless you write it down and revisit it.
Like, I have a whiteboard right here
and it's filled with stuff that I write down,
I erase and I'll write down again.
So yeah, you have to write things down even like with
what you're not happy with
and try to write down why you don't think you're happy.
Mm-Hmm. And then come back to it in a couple days
and then build upon it.
Mm-Hmm. Um, that way you don't keep on revisiting the same
question and it just wastes your time.
So it's just annoying.
And I've noticed, I've said this to a handful
of even close friends and they've se they see me doing
whatever I'm doing and they still don't listen.
So I'm telling you, writing it down is so important
and, and keeping a log.
Um, but
I think that's so critical.
I just, it, I mean, you can call it journaling.
You can just like taking notes, like taking those ideas down
as they come, come to you.
'cause you'll, for, you'll, you'll forget 'em real
quick. And, um,
Yeah. It's annoying.
Yeah, it is. I'm like, what was that?
It was such a good idea. I have, I just use my phone
and I'll just go into notes and I'll just like type in.
Okay. I I saw that
and I'm just gonna give my brain a tiny bit
of capacity there so I can go focus on something else.
But, um, yeah, it's interesting
'cause when you, when you kind of write it out,
you like subconsciously kind
of create it over over time too.
Um, which is really interesting.
'cause I was like, oh, you know, this year this is
what I wanna accomplish, da da da.
And then I look back like two years later, like,
I actually did it and I was like, oh, that's
Sick. There we go. Yeah.
And the numbers were actually very close. Wow.
Very similar. And, uh, and yeah,
and you know, don't get disappointed
with yourself if you don't hit those things,
but just, it is a practice.
Right. It is a discipline.
Um, what are some of the things,
and we only have a few more minutes and
I wanna say hi to Ethan.
Ethan's here has a creative agency. Um,
There we go.
And, uh, he's, yeah, I've seen this guy grow a lot too.
And he's been, um, going through a lot
of different organizational ups
and downs, working with different people.
Um, Ethan, while we have uh, Charlie here,
do you have any questions regarding kind of like operations
or partnerships or, or things like that?
'cause Charlie has a, a ton of experience, um, just
running his own businesses for a while.
Um, not that I can, not that I can think
of right off the bat, but did you, well,
'cause John, you, when you started your first businesses,
you, you did it with partners
and then you've kind of just done it yourself
and now you're with your wife.
So Charlie, is that, is that something similar to you?
Did you start with partners
and are still still going with 'em?
Or are you just by yourself
now and what do you think's better?
Yeah, good question. Um,
so I, I don't believe in partners.
Like, I feel like if you're starting out,
there's no point to have a partner.
Again, take it with a grain of salt.
But most of the time if you have a partner, it's
because both of you guys are gonna be relying on each other
to do a hundred percent, but end up only doing 50% each.
Now with John, I,
so if he's partners with someone in his family.
That's completely different.
You know, that's, that's different.
But for me, I feel like most people will get into a
partnership because they're almost too lazy
to figure out a certain side
because they're just like, I don't want to do this side.
I'm just not good at it and I believe
that you should learn it anyway.
Again, this is not a popular opinion,
but this is just what I've done.
And then after you learn everything,
after you grow at least to a good amount, whatever
that amount is in that industry, then uh, getting a partner
because it's more strategic.
Um, I mean, it's kind of like I won't go too deep in it,
but that's, that's my opinion,
is you gotta be really careful with partners.
'cause it's easy to get into a relationship,
but it's hard to get out.
So just gotta be really careful.
Thank you. That's a great answer.
Yeah, so
I'm sorry I joined late.
I was just having dinner.
I couldn't, I couldn't move it, but
No, that's, that's terrible man.
Don't eat. You're not allowed to eat, dude.
Um, yeah, no, I think that's, no, I'm,
and I'll, I'll be honest, dude, I, I was that guy.
You know, I, I easily partnered up with people
to fulfill a part of the business
that I just didn't understand, or,
or I was too lazy to figure out myself.
And what happened was, when I had done that initially
with my first business is I,
when I had my two other partners, is that they, they,
they put me in a box
and then I did not know how to do X, y, and Z in the company.
And so I was super limited when I had got bought out,
you know, of the, of the company, I was left on my own.
I realized, wow, I don't really know s**t.
Like I was calling myself an entrepreneur
and all this stuff, but like, when it came down to it,
I was like, I, I feel like I'm,
I'm doing this all from the beginning.
And um, and yeah.
And over the years I had partnered up with other people too,
and then I ended up having to kick 'em out
and I had to buy 'em out myself.
And it was just like you said, you're competing for like,
this percentage of work
and then it's like, it's never really balanced.
Um, the reason why me and my wife work is
because like, we f*****g live together, you know?
Every we do, we share everything together.
Yeah. It's your life partner. Yeah.
I mean, that's different man.
And we do, and, and like she's the type, she's like, okay,
like she's so real about stuff
and sometimes I can get my head in the clouds too.
So she kind of brings me back to the level mm-Hmm.
Um, and so that's kind of what I, I,
I thought I needed someone like me.
It's like, no, I needed someone completely opposite of me
who can think some so differently than me.
Um, yeah. And yeah, that's how, that's
how marriage works too and stuff.
But, um, I think we have probably time for like,
one more question for Charlie.
Does anybody have any questions?
And thank you so much for jumping on this, Charlie.
I know this is like Yeah. Out of your, you know, know now.
Yeah. I usually stay really quiet, but No, it was cool.
Yeah, I'm happy. I hope it helps
people see it's just different.
I don't, I don't,
I didn't know if the group is all video editors,
so I was like, is this gonna be helpful?
I didn't really know, but hopefully people found this
helpful and, you know, you know,
it's tough out there. So Yeah,
I think what you said towards the end for sure,
like is so valuable.
I mean, you're talk, we're, at the end of the day,
what keeps us all similar is
like, we're all human beings, right?
And we're all struggling with our own stuff
and to just to hear someone else's perspective.
Um, you know, and insight is like,
like hearing it from your mouth, the way that you said
what you said impacted me,
Right? Oh, nice. There
we go.
And, and I think that's, that's enough.
But yeah, that's awesome.
But I just know other people will also feel the same way.
'cause um, yeah, like I said, beyond the, the tricks
and the strategies and the tips, like man, we're,
we're all just trying to figure it out together.
And um, I think that's what community's all about, you know,
spars said, uh, thank you so much.
Thanks for jumping on. Ethan, do you have a question?
Yeah, I do have a question.
So my kind of plan was, I, I wanted
to start my own e-comm store in,
in maybe a few years down the line.
'cause, so at the moment it is like, uh, video editing,
specialized direct response video, anything like agency.
And now we're moving to more creative strategy and research.
So doing everything. Yeah.
And, but I think
after I've learned all of them skills, then I can kind
of like subcontract it out to my other business.
Do you know what I mean? So then everything's like,
like a monopoly kind of.
But I wanted to start an e-commerce store, um,
because I think it's one of the businesses that is kind
of infinitely scalable.
Do you know what I mean? Amazon is is e-commerce. Yeah.
And with an agency business model, when you have loads
of clients and then it becomes quite hard to manage them all
and Oh, I
See what you mean.
So what, how was, what was your experience like starting,
I'm sure you must have gone through a lot of, um, trial
and error and a lot of failures,
like trying different products and things like that.
Yeah. I know it's left,
but I'd be interested to hear how you started.
Yeah. In the beginning of this loom
or, uh, not loom, uh, zoom.
I kind of mentioned a little bit about it, but as to like,
and I, first of all what you said as far
as it being scalable, that's a really good point.
'cause yeah, clients and yeah, you really do have
to build constant umbrellas of management
and if you're gonna keep scaling like a big agency,
and that's a, that's a really good point.
Um, as far as me starting like e-commerce, you know,
you're already getting so much experience with the clients
that you have, so you can kind
of already see trends and data.
Usually it's hard to develop an eye for a product.
I kind of mentioned in the middle of this,
what I like is if you, um,
do purchase test orders on different stores
that you find are actively running ads, right?
You find a Facebook ad save, find a Facebook ad save,
and then you, if you like five to seven stores,
you place an order on their store with an email, right?
You get that order number and then you cancel, right?
So it's free. Then you wait seven days,
you place another order with a different email cancel,
and then you kind of subtract the orders divide by seven.
Now you get orders per day, you multiply it by their a OV,
whatever you think it is, let's just say it's 50 bucks.
Now you see how much revenue per day they're doing.
You do that across seven different industries
and you say, okay, this one has a lot of opportunity.
Um, and then you have to decide, do you wanna move forward
with that or do you wanna keep playing this game
because you need to also see where is your strong set at?
You're looking at also these opportunities.
Like you'd look at 'em if it was like a broken down house,
like where can you renovate?
So you're looking at it in different angles
and that'll give you a good start on
where to kind of move forward.
Um, yeah.
And then, and then after that, you know,
you'll probably have to go through the same thing,
building a team, but it'll be scalable.
I do like that. And I think there's a lot more data
to optimize from as well.
So I was working with a, an e-commerce brand,
and they shared the results of all the ad performance.
And I was really interested
because like conversion rate is such a big thing.
Like it's, it is influenced by so many different things,
like how your website looks, like, even just the colors
of buttons, the positions.
But then it can also be in influenced by the ad creative
as well and like the specific messaging behind that.
So I do quite like that, that e-commerce literally just
e everything all, all in one.
And there's so much, like, so many variables to
that you can improve.
Yeah. Charlie teaches this stuff.
Do you still, there we go. Yeah. Yeah.
Do you, do you still offer
Your course? Mm-Hmm.
No. I it down, I think I closed it.
Yeah, I closed it like maybe a year ago or so.
Even though it's still, it's really good
content, it's still relevant.
It's just not something that I feel like
unless I'm gonna be actively in it
and updating it consistently, I'd rather come back
and make a whole new course of some sort.
Um, I just like to do things a hundred percent.
I just don't wanna do it half-ass.
And that's just kind of a, a fault at me.
I was always, I've always been like that.
It's a blessing and a curse. Right.
Well, amazing man. Well, um, thank you
so much Charlie, for jumping on.
I, I, I learned a lot
and it definitely got a lot of value from this call
and I'm sure others will.
So, um, thank you for your time man.
And I'm looking to, uh, keep, uh,
keep helping you out on your journey, bro.
And I wish you all the best.
There we go. It was fun hopping on
and yeah, hopefully everyone got some value.
Amazing. All right guys, thank you so much
for jumping on. I'll see you guys in the next one.
Thank you. All right, see ya.
Bye.